

Profile

Dedicated Technical Support Analyst with knowledge of service delivery and proven multitasking abilities. Solid team player with an outgoing, positive demeanor and proven skills in establishing rapport with clients. Specialize in quality, speed, and process optimization. Articulate, energetic, and results-oriented with exemplary passion for developing relationships, cultivating partnerships, and growing businesses.

Employment History

IT Support Analyst, Kian Computers, North York

FEBRUARY 2021 - OCTOBER 2021

- Handled all Customer Service and Support calls and email.
- Worked to motivate and support all creative staff, resulting in excellent workflow and productivity.
- Helped to devise a new business model, and steps to support it.
- Created, resolved, or escalated support tickets.
- Managed front-end and back-end development in the company's Portfolio Analyst, Employee Track, and Account Management systems.

Customer Service Representative, Esso, Toronto

DECEMBER 2018 - DECEMBER 2020

- Maintained customer satisfaction with forward-thinking strategies focused on addressing customer needs and resolving concerns.
- Provided primary customer support to internal and external customers.
- Developed community reputation through commitment to customer satisfaction and strong client relationships.
- Excellent multitasker
- Exhibited high energy and professionalism when dealing with clients and staff
- .

Education

Advanced Diploma, George Brown College, Toronto

SEPTEMBER 2018 - PRESENT

Computer Programming Analyst

Diploma, G-Tech Information Center, Mananthavady

JULY 2017 - OCTOBER 2017

AutoCAD, Adobe Photoshop

Details

North York, M2J1L9 Canada

6478691231

arunmoopatil25@gmail.com

Links

LinkedIn

Portfolio

GitHub

Skills

HTML/CSS/JavaScript

MongoDB

React

Node.js

Python

PHP

MySQL

Git

Figma

Adobe Photoshop

Hobbies

Reading

Coding

Soccer

Badminton